soapdirt.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy | Soap Dirt

**Last updated:** October 6th, 2017

SoapDirt.com is an online service operated in the United States and can be accessed via the internet with a computer, mobile device and other electronic devices,. This “Privacy Policy” applies to this site and other features, applications or downloads that are controlled by us that are available through this site

This Privacy Policy does not apply to collection of information or data from other sources (unless specifically stated).

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of Use posted on our Website, sets forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

We reserve the right to change the privacy policy without prior notice and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the conditions of this privacy policy you should immediately cease visiting the website.

Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”).

**Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze collected information and data.

**Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information. By providing your contact information, you agree to allow us to contact you.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site. Security The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
